Hey.
Where's Mon?
She's at home
putting up decorations
for Rachel's birthday
party tonight.
And you're not helping?
I tried, but apparently
singing "I Will Survive"
in a helium voice-- not helping.
Hey, you guys.
Hey, come on in.
♪ Happy birth... ♪
Shh! Don't say that loud.
Gunther's going
to want to hug me.
Good news, everyone.
We finally found
a nanny.
This is Molly.
Molly...
Chandler, Joey.
Hi.
( baby crying )
Oops, somebody's
getting a little fussy.
You're damn right I am.
I've been waiting
for a cookie for seven minutes.
Okay. You know what?
I'm just going
to take her outside.
No, you stay.
I'll do it.
Okay, thank you.
Nice to meet you guys.
JOEY:
Yeah, you, too.
Wow, Molly's just great.
Yes, bravo on
the hot nanny.
What?
You really think
she's hot?
Are you kidding?
If I wasn't married,
she'd be rejecting me right now.
Joey?
How do you think she's doing?
Am I the only one
that doesn't think
that she's hot, Ross?
Eh. I mean, I mean
she's not unattractive
but, but, hot? Eh.
Thank you.
Now that Rachel's gone?
So hot, I cried
myself to sleep last night.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, Mike, what's
the capital of Peru?
Lima.
No.
Um, it starts with a V
and ends with an X
and hopefully with a T, O
in the middle.
You know,
come to think of it
the capital of Peru is VTOX.
What?
Oh, God!
Okay, I don't want
to freak you out
or anything
but I think I just saw
a rat in your cupboard.
Oh, yeah. No, that's Bob.
He's your pet rat?
Well, not so much a pet
as, you know,
an occasional visitor
who I put food out for,
you know.
Kind of like Santa.
Except Santa doesn't poop
on the plate of cookies.
You can't keep a rat
in your apartment.
They're extremely unsanitary.
They transmit leptospirosis
and hantavirus.
What are those?
I don't know, but they don't
sound like spa treatments.
You have to get rid of it.
Okay, fine.
If it means that much to you,
I'll get rid of Bob.
Thank you.
It's just so weird
that you think
he's so gross
yet you're willing
to eat his crackers.
Hello.
Gavin, I just want
to say thank you again
for watching Emma yesterday
during the presentation.
I really owe you an apology.
For what?
Well, when we first met,
you know,
I thought you were pompous
and arrogant and obnoxious.
Is this your first apology?
I just mean that, you know,
first impressions
don't mean anything.
I think you're really a good guy
and I'm sorry
that I misjudged you.
Good morning.
Hello.
But you know what?
Hey, new day,
new leaf.
I am just really,
really happy...
I'm sorry.
Obviously, Heather's ass
has something
more important to say
so I'll just wait
till it's finished.
What?
I was giving you
an apology
and you were totally
checking her out.
I wasn't checking her out.
I'm in fashion.
I was looking at her skirt.
Or was it pants?
I didn't really see what
happened below the ass area.
Oh, you are really,
really a creep.
What do you even care
if I was looking at her?
Are you jealous?
Oh, yeah, I'm jealous.
Oh, Gavin, please,
please look at my ass.
Stop looking at my ass!
I mean,
I just think
you are totally
inappropriate, okay?
This is a work environment.
She's your subordinate.
But it was okay
when you slept
with your old assistant Tag?
That is totally different,
for two reasons:
One-- I didn't know
that you knew that;
and two-- I wasn't
some creep staring at his ass.
We had a, we had a deep,
meaningful relationship.
Huh? What was Tag's last name?
It was...
Oh, my God.
He didn't, he didn't have
a last name.
It was just Tag.
You know, like Cher or...
you know, Moses.
But it was a deep,
meaningful relationship.
Oh, you know what?
My first impression of you
was absolutely right.
You are arrogant,
you are pompous.
Morgan! Morgan! Tag's last name
was Morgan! Ha!
It was Jones.
What are you, his boyfriend?
Man, I wish I had
a nanny like you.
You mean, when you
were a baby?
Sure.
Would you stop
staring at her?
I wasn't staring.
I was leering.
What's the big deal
with her?
Maybe she's attractive
in an obvious kind of way.
Yeah, obvious beauty's
the worst.
You know, when it's right there
in your face?
Me, I like to have to work
to find someone attractive.
Makes me feel like I earned it.
Looks like Joey's
doing all right
with her.
Yeah. Hey that was nice
of you guys to back off
and let Joey
get the girl for once.
I'm going to take her
back to the apartment.
Okay, I'll be home
right after work.
Okay.
Okay, bye, Emma
wemma demma.
I luvvy wuvvy duv you.
Bye.
They elected me
to talk to you
about the baby talk.
It's not so good.
I think it's sweet.
ALL:
Bye, Emma wemma demma!
Hey, listen, Joey,
about Molly.
I would really prefer
if you didn't go after her.
Why not?
Because it took us months
to find a good nanny
and I wouldn't want anything
to, you know, drive her away.
So, what, you think
I'm just going to sleep with her
and never call her again
and things are going
to get uncomfortable?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Come on.
There are plenty
of other women
out there, okay?
Just forget
about her, okay?
She's off-limits.
Oh, man. Why'd you have to go
and say that for?
Now that you told me
I can't have her
it makes me want her even more.
What are you,
a child?
Yes.
Joey, come on now.
For me, please?
Just try to focus
your sexual energy
on someone else.
All right.
Take me home.
Hey, Mikey.
Hey, Pheeb.
What are you doing?
Setting rat traps.
To kill Bob?
No, no. To test
his neck strength.
But no, Mike,
I don't want to kill him.
I thought we were just
going to capture him
and, you know, set him free
in the countryside
where he could maybe meet,
you know, a friendly possum
and a wisecracking owl.
Okay, okay.
I'll throw away
the traps.
All right.
I'll find Bob.
I'll get him.
Bob?
Bob?!
Robert!
( squeaking )
Oh, wait.
I think I hear him.
Oh, my God!
Bob had babies!
Bob's a mom!
We'll have to think
of a new name for her.
Oh, I don't know.
I kind of like "Bob"
for a girl.
I'm not sure...
( loud snap )
Oh, my God,
we killed Bob?
Well, maybe it wasn't Bob.
Maybe it was a mouse.
Suzy?!
Wassup!
Seriously, dude,
three years ago.
Okay.
Listen, can you do me
a favor?
I'm going
to be out today.
Can you just keep
an eye on Joey?
Make sure nothing happens
between him and Molly?
You don't trust him?
No.
Some woman who sounded
a lot like Joey called earlier
and asked for her daughter,
"The hot nanny."
Is this really
your long-term plan
for me to run
interference?
Because I could get
a job any day now.
You do appear
right on the cusp
of something.
Look, come on, man.
I'm sure he'll lose
interest in a week or two
but for now, could you please
just do this for me?
All right, fine.
But don't blame me
if it doesn't work.
'Cause you know
as well as I do
once Joey sets him mind
on something
more often than not,
he's going to have sex with it.
Well, we got to do something,
okay?
Nannies like her
don't grow on trees.
Picturing that tree?
I am, yes.
Where you going, Joe?
For a walk.
Oh, you mind if join you?
Actually, I'd rather
be alone, you know?
I really need
to organize my thoughts.
Your thoughts?
Plural?
All right, fine.
I only have one thought.
It's about the hot nanny!
I got to see her!
I'm afraid I can't
let you do that, Joe.
Now you're telling me
I can't see her.
You guys are killing me.
She's forbidden fruit.
It's like, like...
like she's the princess
and I'm the stable boy.
Why are you doing this, huh?
Did Ross tell you
not to let me go over there?
Yes, as a matter
of fact he did
so I can't let you go.
Huh, interesting.
Now there are obstacles.
Hot nanny and me
against the world.
This is the kind of stuff
great novels are made of.
Great novels?
Fine. Mediocre porn.
( phone rings )
Gavin Mitchell's office.
Rachel Green's office.
Give me that phone.
Hello, this is Rachel Green.
How can I help you?
Uh-huh. Okay then.
I'll pass you back to your son.
Hey, Mom.
No, that's just my secretary.
Um, excuse me, Gavin.
I have a question
I need to ask you.
Mom, I'll call you later.
Yes?
If you like looking
at butts so much
why don't you just go
look in a mirror?
Thank God,
you finally said that.
I saw you make a note
on your pad three hours ago.
You know what?
Man, I really bug you, don't I?
Oh, no, please.
I don't care about you
enough to bug me.
In fact, from now on,
I'm going to take the high road
and I'm going to be
very, very nice to you
you mama's boy,
starting right now.
( knocking )
Hey, Rach.
Hey, you ready
for your birthday lunch?
I am, I am.
Oh, but first, Monica
I would like
to introduce you
to my very talented colleague
and more importantly,
my wonderful friend,
Gavin Mitchell.
Pleased to meet you.
So are you coming to
Rachel's party tonight?
Oh, no, no, no.
Gavin can't.
He already has plans.
Most likely with his mother.
Well, I don't mind.
I'll cancel them.
I would never miss
my secretary's birthday.
( hushed ):
God! Why did you
invite him?!
I can't stand that guy!
You were just being
so nice to him.
I was faking it.
Can't you tell
when I'm being fake?
Hey, Mr. Phillips.
Nice suit.
Right there!
That was so fake!
Shh... shh!
Oh, hi.
I still can't believe
you invited Gavin.
I mean, he is just the last
person I want to see.
Well, you're welcome
for the party.
I'm glad you're
having a good time.
God, I hope
he doesn't show up.
Of course he's not
going to show up.
The guys hates me.
Does he?
What?
Maybe he keeps
bothering you so much
because he likes you.
Like in first grade
when Skippy Lange
would always push me
on the playground
because he secretly
had a crush on me.
Oh, Monica, you think
Skippy liked you?
Honey, all those boys
had a bet
to see if he could
knock you over.
She' out. I'm going
to take her home.
Oh, okay, thank you.
Bye, sweetheart.
Do you see what all
the guys see in her?
Wouldn't kick her
out of bed.
No more vodka for me.
Hey, Rach.
Yeah.
So can I sing
"Happy Birthday"
to you now?
Yeah, sure.
Ah, all right.
♪ Happy birth... ♪
See you later.
Hey, Rach.
Yeah?
Somebody got
you shoes.
Oh, gimme!
Wow! Wow...
( screams )
Oh, my God!
Careful, careful.
These are my rat babies.
Yeah, we have
rat babies now.
Oh, you brought rats
to my birthday party?
So this is what
a stroke feels like.
I had to bring them.
We killed their mother.
They're our
responsibility now.
You know, they require
constant care.
You should know
that, Rachel.
You're a mother.
Are you comparing my daughter
to a rat?
No, seven rats.
I think we should
take them home.
We need to feed them.
You're going to leave
my party to take care
of a box of rats?
I'm sorry, Rachel,
but I'm not like you, okay?
Not everyone can afford help.
Hey, where the hell
are Joey and Molly?
I asked you to watch them.
( helium voice ):
I'm sorry. I got
a little preoccupied.
Look, we have to stop them
before something happens.
Right behind
you, big guy.
So, you see, Molly,
what people don't understand
is that acting is
a discipline.
It takes a lot
of hard work.
So where'd you study?
Oh, I didn't go to college.
No, where'd you
study acting?
Molly... people don't
study acting.
ROSS:
Molly, uh...
uh, do you mind giving us
just a minute?
Sure. I'll go check on Emma.
Thanks.
Will the stable boy
never get the princess?
So, what?
What did you think
you were going to do, huh
have sex with her
right here on my couch?
No.
The leather sticks
to my ass.
This isn't fair.
What makes you think
that I'm just going
to sleep with her
and then blow her off, huh?
Can't you guys
open your minds
to the possibility
that I actually like her
and might want
something real?
Look, the truth is
I haven't felt this way
about anyone since Rachel.
I didn't think I could
ever love again.
Come on!
Joey!
All right.
( knocking )
Hi.
Is Molly here?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Come on in. Molly.
Oh, hey.
Guys, this is Tabitha.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Uh, well, Joey, I... I guess
we have no problem.
It's like my favorite
fairy tale come true.
The princess, the stable boy
and the lesbian.
Okay, you start
preparing the formula
and I'll start
changing the box
and then we've got to put
them straight to bed.
Hey, when did we become
one of those couples
whose lives revolve
around their rats?
Well, you know what,
they're our responsibility now.
Okay, fine.
These rats are
our responsibility.
But what happens when they mate
and there are hundreds of them?
Mate? They're all
brothers and sisters.
Yeah, not such
a problem with rats.
They're more of a
"love the one your with"
kind of animal.
No. Really?
Oh, get off your sister!
Ew.
Oh, my God, what
are we going to do?
We have seven rats.
Mm-hmm.
So what if...
what if each of
them has seven rats
and then each of those
has seven rats?
That's like...
That's math I can't
even do.
What are we
going to do?
I know this is going
to sound crazy--
but we could not let the box
of rats ruin our lives.
Yeah, okay.
I guess you're right.
All right, so we should
just give them away.
But to nice families,
with children
and Reduced Fat Wheat Thins.
Those are Bob's favorite.
It's going to be okay.
You must think
I'm crazy.
No, I think you're sweet.
Good.
It's just so hard.
It's hard for me
to let them go.
I guess it just
brings back memories
you know from...
when I gave birth
to my brother's triplets
and I had to give them up.
I haven't told you
about that yet, have I?
Hey.
Hi.
Thanks for the party, honey.
Should I help
you clean up?
No, way.
You had your party,
now I have mine.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, I just get
a little bummed
when my birthday's over.
Well, at least you have
one thing to be happy about.
Hmm?
That jerk Gavin
from your office
didn't show up.
Yeah, I hate him.
Oh, we weren't
talking about you.
No. No way to recover.
Uh-uh.
Okay.
Fun party.
Well, it was.
And you would
have seen it
if you didn't show up at...
9:30?
God, this party was lame.
Again, you're welcome.
Look, I'll just
give you this and go.
Oh, you bought
me a present. Why?
Let me explain how
birthday parties
usually work.
There are presents
and a cake
perhaps a fourth
or fifth person.
No. Okay....
I got you the present
to make up for being
such a jerk to you.
Ah.
Well, okay, well,
that's very nice.
And you wrote a card.
"From Gavin."
I really mean it.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, it's beautiful.
If you don't mind, let me...
Well...
what do you know?
It fits.
See, Gavin, you're
capable of being a nice guy.
Why do you give me
such a hard time?
I'm not sure.
Well, Monica seems
to think
it's because you have
feelings for me.
I do have feelings
for you.
You do?
Yes, I feel that you're
a little annoying.
See, why, Gavin, why?
Right when I'm about
to change my opinion of you
you go and you...
...and you do that.
( helium voice ):
♪ First I was afraid ♪
♪ I was petrified... ♪
Hey.
Listen, I think
I left something here.
Oh, well
somebody left this.
Is this yours?
Ooh, no, but
I like it.
No, I think I left
one of rat babies.
Oh, uh, no, I haven't seen it
but if I do, I'll let you know.
Rat baby!
Rat baby! Rat baby!
Oh, maybe that's him.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org